Inventory of the Devin A. Garrity papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Devin A. Garrity papers
1912-1981
82032
Hoover Institution Archives
51 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box, 29 motion picture film reels (23.8 linear feet)
Correspondence, manuscripts and galleys of books, reviews, printed matter, photographs, and motion picture film relating to publishing activities of the Devin-Adair Company.
Garrity, Devin A.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1982.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Biographical Note
American publisher; president, Devin-Adair Company, 1939-1981.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, manuscripts, published materials, reviews, articles, photographs, and motion picture film relating to the publishing activities of the Devin-Adair Company and editor-in-chief Devin A. Garrity. Subjects of interest include ecological conservation, Irish culture, Africa, Spain, and conservative politics in America. Includes comprehensive alphabetical lists of correspondence and published authors.
Devin-Adair Company.; Motion pictures.; Publishers and publishing--United States.
- Biographical File, 1954-1980
  - Articles and speeches, 1954-1980 (Box-folder 19: 2-4)
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes correspondence, newsletters, news clippings, and writings of Devin Garrity and others.
  - Articles and notes, general, 1957 April-1970 November (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Head shots, photographs, 1965 (Box-folder 20: 7)
  - Personal file, correspondence, articles, 1969 November-1971 June (Box-folder 23: 7)
- Correspondence, 1938-1981
  - General, 1939-1980
    Includes correspondence with multiple authors and general subjects.
    - 1939-1963 April (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - 1949 September-1979 March (Box-folder 45: 6)
    - 1951 July-1976 August (Box-folder 20: 1)
    - 1952 January-1972 February (Box-folder 47: 7)
    - 1967 December-1972 May (Box-folder 47: 8)
    - 1972 July-1980 December (Box-folder 47: 1)
    - For signature, 1970 January-1976 November (Box-folder 45: 7)
    - Flynn-F.D.R, 1950 April-1961 November (Box-folder 29: 6)
      Also includes miscellaneous columns, articles, and newspaper clippings.
    - American Book Club, Gordon Schendel, Herbert Sass, 1950 November-1965 August (Box-folder 20: 8)
      Also includes articles.
    - Donal Rechberg and Fred Hartley, 1955 February-1958 March (Box-folder 51: 19)
    - William F. Buckley, B. H. Liddell Hart, et al., 1956 February-1959 February (Box-folder 51: 7)
    - Victor von Hagen, Marjory Sanger, and Richard C. Potter, 1957 March-1958 January (Box-folder 51: 11)
    - George R. Jordan, Louis P. Lochner, et al., 1958 January-1963 September (Box-folder 51: 13)
    - William La Varre, Admiral Karl Donitz, et al., 1958 February-1962 May (Box-folder 51: 14)
    - Alden Stahr, Herbert R. Sass, et al., 1958 April-December (Box-folder 51: 15)
    - Otto Eisenschiml and Raphael Plumpelly, 1958 September-1959 November (Box-folder 50: 12)
    - James Plunkett, Elizabeth Rivers, et al., 1961 July-1963 March (Box-folder 51: 10)
    - C.L. Sonnichsen, U.T.E.P., 1966 January-1968 October (Box-folder 25: 6)
      Also includes articles and newspaper clippings.
    - Graham Carey, Christopher Derrick, and C. Stillman, 1966 July-1968 January (Box-folder 19: 1)
    - Good Health To You, 1969 September (Box-folder 47: 2)
    - Al J. Venter and Zambesi Salient, 1974 July-1975 July (Box-folder 37: 20)
      Also includes receipts.
  - Alphabetical, 1938-1981
    - A
      - 1953 January-July (Box-folder 23: 8)
      - 1961 December-1967 January (Box-folder 13: 10)
      - 1964 October-1965 December (Box-folder 15: 4)
      - 1977-1979 July (Box-folder 40: 5-6)
      - Gregory Allen, 1957 December-1962 November (Box-folder 51: 6)
    - B
      - 1958 January-1960 November (Box-folder 51: 4)
      - 1961 December-1963 December (Box-folder 23: 1)
      - 1965 February-December (Box-folder 15: 2)
      - 1966 February-1967 January (Box-folder 13: 6)
      - 1967 January-December (Box-folder 26: 8)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 40: 7)
      - 1979 October-November (Box-folder 39: 4)
      - John W. Blodgett, Jr., 1973 January-1977 February (Box-folder 40: 9)
      - John N. Booth, 1976 (Box-folder 49: 1)
        Also includes a newsletter.
    - C
      - 1959 March-1961 October (Box-folder 23: 2)
      - 1965 January-December (Box-folder 15: 3)
      - 1965 December-1966 December (Box-folder 13: 5)
      - 1978 October-November (Box-folder 39: 5)
      - 1979 August-September (Box-folder 39: 6)
      - Philip S. Callahan, 1975 July-1977 December (Box-folder 48: 1)
      - Norine Campbell, 1973 July-1981 February (Box-folder 39: 3)
      - Linda Clark, 1975 November-1977 November (Box-folder 48: 4)
      - Stuart Cloete, 1964 November-1965 March (Box-folder 51: 20)
        Also includes clippings.
      - Dorothy Crispo, 1973 August-1975 November (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - D
      - 1957 December-1963 November (Box-folder 36: 18)
      - 1965 February-1966 September (Box-folder 15: 1)
      - 1966 February-December (Box-folder 13: 4)
      - 1967 January-December (Box-folder 26: 7)
      - 1979 October (Box-folder 39: 10)
      - Christopher Derrick, 1972 February-1977 February (Box-folder 48: 5)
      - John Henry Dick, 1971 February-1980 November (Box-folder 39: 9)
      - Lord Dunsany, 1953 August-November (Box-folder 37: 23)
    - E
      - 1958 December-1961 September (Box-folder 24: 8)
      - 1962 January-1963 April (Box-folder 36: 17)
      - 1964 December-1966 November (Box-folder 13: 3)
      - 1965 February-December (Box-folder 16: 14)
      - 1966 June-1967 December (Box-folder 26: 6)
      - 1978 January-July (Box-folder 39: 13)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 39: 11)
      - Catharyn Elwood, 1958 January-1963 September (Box-folder 36: 16)
      - Catharyn Elwood, 1973 May-1975 October (Box-folder 48: 6)
      - Julius Epstein, 1955 August-1975 November (Box-folder 48: 2)
    - F
      - 1961 January-1962 December (Box-folder 36: 4)
      - 1964 June-1965 December (Box-folder 16: 13)
      - 1966 February-November (Box-folder 13: 2)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 26: 2)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 39: 14)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 39: 16)
    - G
      - 1961 April-1963 November (Box-folder 36: 5)
      - 1965 February-1966 February (Box-folder 16: 12)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 13: 1)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 26: 5)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 39: 17)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 39: 18)
    - H
      - 1961 March-1963 January (Box-folder 36: 7)
      - 1964 December-1965 December (Box-folder 16: 11)
      - 1966 February-1967 June (Box-folder 14: 3)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 26: 4)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 39: 19)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 39: 20)
      - Maurice Hennessy, 1974 March-1980 November (Box-folder 39: 22)
    - I
      - 1962 (Box-folder 36: 10)
      - 1964 October-1966 December (Box-folder 14: 4)
      - 1964 December-1965 November (Box-folder 16: 10)
      - 1967 March-October (Box-folder 26: 3)
      - 1977 October-1978 June (Box-folder 39: 24)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - J
      - 1961 February-1962 February (Box-folder 36: 9)
      - 1965 March-October (Box-folder 16: 9)
      - 1966 February-October (Box-folder 14: 5)
      - 1967 May-December (Box-folder 26: 1)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 2)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 4)
      - Wallace Johnson, 1975 July-1976 November (Box-folder 38: 3)
      - Dorothea V.G. Jones, 1973 August (Box-folder 48: 3)
    - K
      - 1961 February-1963 March (Box-folder 36: 8)
      - 1964 December-1966 March (Box-folder 16: 8)
      - 1966 February-December (Box-folder 14: 10)
      - 1966 October-1967 December (Box-folder 27: 10)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 5)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 6)
      - Howard Kershner, 1971 April-1979 August (Box-folder 49: 16)
    - K-L, 1961 April-1963 August (Box-folder 13: 7)
    - L
      - 1961 March-1963 September (Box-folder 36: 11)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 16: 6)
      - 1966 February-December (Box-folder 14: 6)
      - 1966 December-1968 December (Box-folder 24: 5)
      - 1967 January-November (Box-folder 27: 9)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 10)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 11)
      - Lee Layton, 1975 October (Box-folder 46: 2)
      - Dell Leonardi, 1975 March-1976 July (Box-folder 49: 14)
      - Dell Leonardi, 1977 January-1980 January (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - M
      - 1955 August-1966 December (Box-folder 14: 22)
      - 1958 August-1961 August (Box-folder 50: 3)
      - 1961 January-1963 October (Box-folder 51: 2)
      - 1964 December-1966 February (Box-folder 16: 5)
      - 1966 September-1967 December (Box-folder 27: 6)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 27: 5)
      - 1969 January-October (Box-folder 24: 6)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 12)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 18)
      - Seumas MacManus, 1957 September-1958 November (Box-folder 50: 2)
      - Jorge Manach, 1950 (Box-folder 51: 17)
      - Wayne Martin, 1948-1976 April (Box-folder 36: 1)
      - Wayne Martin, 1975 February-1977 December (Box-folder 49: 17)
      - Wayne Martin, 1977 November-1979 November (Box-folder 38: 16)
      - Denis Meadows, 1959 June-1963 September (Box-folder 50: 1)
        Also includes notes.
      - John F. Montgomery, 1947 May-1949 September (Box-folder 50: 11)
        Also includes clippings and a photograph.
      - Friederich Morton, 1959 November-1960 October (Box-folder 50: 6)
      - Adolph Murie, 1953 May-1964 April (Box-folder 50: 10)
      - Joseph F. Murphy, 1972 February-1979 November (Box-folder 38: 15)
    - Mc
      - 1962 January-1963 February (Box-folder 51: 3)
      - 1965 March-October (Box-folder 16: 4)
      - 1966 March-December (Box-folder 14: 7)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 27: 4)
      - Lewis McCabe and Eliot Macy, 1978 March-1979 March (Box-folder 38: 14)
      - John E. McHale, 1980 October-1981 September (Box-folder 38: 13)
    - N
      - 1961 August-1962 November (Box-folder 23: 9)
      - 1964 June-1968 August (Box-folder 24: 2)
      - 1965 January-November (Box-folder 16: 3)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 14: 11)
      - 1966 May-1967 December (Box-folder 27: 1)
      - 1978 June (Box-folder 38: 22)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 38: 19)
    - O
      - 1964 December-1965 December (Box-folder 16: 2)
      - 1966 February-November (Box-folder 14: 23)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 28: 8)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 23)
      - D.J. O'Sullivan, 1961 October-December (Box-folder 51: 8)
    - O-P, 1968 (Box-folder 25: 10)
    - P
      - 1958 July-1963 June (Box-folder 23: 11)
      - 1965 February-September (Box-folder 16: 1)
      - 1966 February-December (Box-folder 14: 24)
      - 1966 October-1968 December (Box-folder 24: 1)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 28: 5)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 38: 26)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 28: 27)
      - Ray Paige, 1980 March-December (Box-folder 38: 20)
    - Q
      - 1965 April-1966 December (Box-folder 14: 25)
      - 1967 February-October (Box-folder 28: 4)
      - 1968 January (Box-folder 25: 9)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 28: 28)
    - R
      - 1960 June-1963 June (Box-folder 23: 12)
      - 1965 January-November (Box-folder 18: 13)
      - 1966 January-1967 April (Box-folder 15: 10)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 28: 3)
      - 1968 January-October (Box-folder 25: 8)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 37: 4)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 37: 3)
      - Bargyla Rateavar, 1974 January-December (Box-folder 49: 10)
      - Eschel Rhoodie, 1964 June-1965 March (Box-folder 51: 18)
      - Guy Richards, 1973 October-1977 July (Box-folder 49: 13)
      - Francis H. Rigney, 1974 April-1981 February (Box-folder 28: 29)
      - Selden Rodman, 1977 January-1980 May (Box-folder 38: 25)
      - E. Merrill Root, 1938-1955 December (Box-folder 50: 7)
        Also includes flyers.
    - S
      - 1961 April-1963 July (Box-folder 23: 10)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 18: 12)
      - 1965 November-1966 December (Box-folder 15: 9)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 28: 2)
      - 1968 January-November (Box-folder 25: 7)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 37: 8)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 37: 5)
      - John Scott (Water Books), 1976 September-1977 November (Box-folder 37: 6)
      - Ruth W. Shaw, 1970 June-1976 April (Box-folder 49: 9)
      - Ruth Stout, 1972 February-1974 August (Box-folder 49: 8)
    - T
      - 1961 January-September (Box-folder 24: 10)
      - 1962 January-1963 November (Box-folder 36: 12)
      - 1963 December-1965 December (Box-folder 18: 11)
      - 1966 February-1968 February (Box-folder 15: 8)
      - 1966 December-1967 December (Box-folder 28: 1)
      - 1968 February-October (Box-folder 25: 5)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 37: 11)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 37: 9)
      - Lavinia Trevor, London, 1974 March-1976 May (Box-folder 49: 11)
    - U
      - 1962 July-October (Box-folder 36: 15)
      - 1966 September-November (Box-folder 15: 7)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 29: 9)
      - 1968 January-October (Box-folder 25: 4)
      - 1978 January-June (Box-folder 37: 12)
    - V
      - 1962 January-1963 January (Box-folder 36: 14)
      - 1964 September-1968 October (Box-folder 25: 3)
      - 1965 January-November (Box-folder 18: 10)
      - 1966 February-October (Box-folder 15: 7)
      - 1967 March-December (Box-folder 29: 8)
      - 1978 May-July (Box-folder 37: 19)
      - 1979 May-October (Box-folder 37: 13)
    - W
      - 1960 December-1961 December (Box-folder 51: 1)
      - 1961 April-1963 May (Box-folder 13: 9)
      - 1962 October-1963 August (Box-folder 36: 13)
      - 1965 February-1966 December (Box-folder 18: 8)
      - 1966 February-December (Box-folder 15: 6)
      - 1967 February-November (Box-folder 28: 6)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 25: 2)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 37: 18)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 37: 14)
      - A.C. Wedemeyer, 1973 June-1981 February (Box-folder 37: 17)
      - William White, Sweet Wild World: Thoreau on Birds and Small Creatures, 1979 October-1981 April (Box-folder 37: 16)
      - G. Carl Wiegand, 1977 April-1979 April (Box-folder 37: 15)
      - Victor Wierwille, 1971 May-1976 January (Box-folder 49: 12)
    - X-Y-Z
      - 1966 February-November (Box-folder 15: 5)
      - 1967 July-December (Box-folder 28: 7)
      - 1968 February-November (Box-folder 25: 1)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 37: 21)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 37: 22)
      - Ernst Zaugg, 1962 July (Box-folder 13: 8)
- Authors File, 1912-1981
  Includes correspondence, reviews, and manuscripts. Arranged alphabetically by author.
  - Karl Anders, Murder To Order, 1955 June (Box-folder 31: 12)
    Includes clippings and press releases.
  - Carol K. Anthony, Empire: A Study Of World Powers, 1963 September-1965 April (Box-folder 8: 1)
    Includes manuscript and correspondence.
  - Anne Armstrong, Attentat: A Drama in Four Acts, 1944 July (Box-folder 9: 1)
    Includes manuscript.
  - Will Avery, A Call To Revolution, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 44: 2-7)
  - Karl Baarslag, assorted titles, 1944 December-1980 October (Box-folder 40: 8)
    Includes correspondence and writing samples.
  - Lafayette C. Baker, "Did Stanton Plan Lincoln's Murder?,", 1961 August (Box-folder 46: 10)
    Includes a magazine article.
  - Stephen Barber, America in Retreat, 1970 May-July (Box-folder 35: 5-6)
    Includes correspondence and manuscript.
  - Harry E. Barnes, Italian Foreign Policy Under Mussolini, 1956 January-July (Box-folder 36: 3)
    Includes correspondence.
  - General Tom Barry, Guerrilla Days in Ireland, 1955 April-1956 February (Box-folder 11: 2)
    Includes correspondence and a press release.
  - J.W. Batchelder, Metric Madness, 1981 (Box-folder 46: 4-5)
  - Elizabeth Bentley, Out of Bondage, 1951 January-1953 September (Box-folder 29: 10)
    Includes press releases, reviews, and newspaper clippings.
  - Elizabeth Bentley, Out Of Bondage, 1951 January-1963 April (Box-folder 51: 16)
    Includes correspondence and order forms.
  - Elmer Berger, Partisan History and Judaism, 1952 March-1957 January (Box-folder 31: 21)
    Includes articles, clippings, and correspondence.
  - Charles Bewley, Concentration Camp Europe, 1953 May (Box-folder 34: 6)
  - Charles Bewley, Herman Goering and the Third Reich, 1951 May-1963 March (Box-folder 29: 7)
    Includes correspondence, reviews, and newspaper clippings.
  - Judge Tom Blaine, They Open Prison Doors, 1974 January (Box-folder 7: 5-6)
  - Samuel L. Blumenfeld, Is Public Education Necessary?, 1980 March-August (Box-folder 39: 1)
    Includes correspondence and articles.
  - Hugh A. Brown, Popular Wisdom For Survival, 1954 October-1959 June (Box-folder 50: 5)
    Includes correspondence, reviews, and manuscripts.
  - Lawrence R. Brown, Beyond Conservatism, undated (Box-folder 10: 4)
  - Lawrence R. Brown, The Might of the West Vol. II, undated (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Edgar C. Bundy, Collectivism in the Churches, 1956 December-1963 January (Box-folder 10: 2)
    Includes correspondence and a newsletter.
  - Edgar C. Bundy, Collectivism in the Churches, 1958 February-1964 May (Box-folder 29: 11)
    Includes press releases, newsletters, and newspaper clippings.
  - Grant C. Butler, Kings and Camels: An American in Saudi Arabia, 1959 November-1968 March (Box-folder 29: 4)
    Includes articles and reviews.
  - Philip S. Callahan, 1977 September-1980 January (Box-folder 39: 7)
    Includes correspondence, articles, and writing samples.
  - Eliane Carley, French Gastronomy Through the Ages, 1975 January-1980 May (Box-folder 39: 8)
  - Eugene Castle, Billions, Blunders and Baloney, 1954 January-1955 January (Box-folder 11: 5)
    Includes correspondence, order forms, and table of contents.
  - Eugene Castle, Billions, Blunders and Baloney, 1955 January-1960 February (Box-folder 29: 5)
    Includes articles, reviews, and newspaper clippings.
  - Frank Chodorov, One Is a Crowd, 1952 September-1962 December (Box-folder 31: 3)
    Includes reviews, clippings, and press releases.
  - Frank Chodorov, Out of Step, 1962 (Box-folder 32: 5)
    Includes reviews, advertisements, and articles.
  - Richard C. Clark, Technological Terrorism, 1973 February-1979 July (Box-folder 41: 1-3)
    Includes manuscript, articles, and clippings.
  - Farley Clinton, Fierce Loyalties, A Biography of Fr. Charles Coughlin, 1975 June-July (Box-folder 45: 1-3)
  - Dewitt Copp and Marshall Peck, Betrayal at the U.N., 1961 January-1963 February (Box-folder 32: 7)
    Includes press releases, clippings, and pamphlets.
  - Padraic Colum, Maurice Joy, et al., The Irish Rebellion of 1916 and Its Martyrs: Erin's Tragic Easter, 1916 November-1935 August (Box-folder 4: 3)
    Includes reviews, correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
  - Raymond B. Cowles, From the Bondage of Human Numbers, 1967 (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - Andrieu d'Albas, Death of a Navy, 1957 February-1958 December (Box-folder 32: 6)
    Includes correspondence, clippings, and advertisements.
  - Eldorous L. Dayton, Give 'Em Hell Harry: The Anatomy of the Terrible Tempered Mr. T., 1955 October-1957 March (Box-folder 4: 5)
    Includes forward and correspondence.
  - Eldorous L. Dayton, Give 'Em Hell Harry: The Anatomy of the Terrible Tempered Mr. T., 1956 August-1957 January (Box-folder 32: 9)
    Includes clippings, press releases, and articles.
  - Pete Dayton, Walter Reuther, 1957 November-1958 November (Box-folder 32: 8)
  - John D. Davies, 1966 April-1967 May (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - Somerset de Chair, The Getty Tapes, undated (Box-folder 34: 3-4)
  - Lourenco de Salvador, The World Without Conscience, 1965-1966 October (Box-folder 46: 6)
  - Lev E. Dobrainsky, Russia, USSR and U.S., 1969 August-1971 July (Box-folder 47: 7)
    Includes reviews and manuscript.
  - Bella V. Dodd, School of Darkness, 1963 November-1967 December (Box-folder 32: 10)
    Includes press releases, clippings, and articles.
  - Max Eastman, Reflections on the Failure of Socialism, 1955 March-1966 (Box-folder 32: 11)
    Includes clippings, newsletters, and correspondence.
  - George T. Eggleston, Roosevelt, Churchill and Me, 1973 February-1979 May (Box-folder 41: 4-5)
    Includes manuscript, notes, and correspondence.
  - George T. Eggleston, Roosevelt, Churchill, and the World War II Opposition, 1979 (Box-folder 40: 1-4)
  - George T. Eggleston, Roosevelt, Churchill, and the World War II Opposition, 1979 (Box-folder 41: 6)
    Includes manuscript and pamphlets.
  - Paul E. Eisler, How to Listen to Music, 1973 September-1978 January (Box-folder 39: 12)
    Includes correspondence, outline, and notes.
  - Richard Emerson, The Real Adolf Hitler, undated (Box-folder 46: 8)
  - M. Stanton Evans, The Liberal Establishment, 1965 September-1968 October (Box-folder 32: 13)
    Includes clippings and advertisements.
  - M. Stanton Evans, The Politics of Surrender, 1967 June-1968 June (Box-folder 32: 12)
    Includes press releases, articles, and newsletters.
  - Violet Fenelon, Timothy Tuft, 1970 December (Box-folder 47: 4)
  - Louis Finkelstein, The Jewish Religion: Its Beliefs and Practices, 1962 March (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - John T. Flynn, 1950 February-1958 May (Box-folder 29: 2)
    Includes reviews, pamphlets, articles, and newspaper clippings.
  - John T. Flynn, Decline Of The American Republic and How to Rebuild It, 1955 February-1957 March (Box-folder 10: 5)
  - John T. Flynn, The Lattimore Story, 1950 May-1953 May (Box-folder 31: 1)
    Includes reviews and clippings.
  - John T. Flynn, The Lattimore Story, 1953 February-1954 January (Box-folder 37: 24)
  - John T. Flynn, The Road Ahead, 1950 February-1955 January (Box-folder 31: 7)
    Includes clippings, reviews, and pamphlets.
  - John T. Flynn, The Roosevelt Myth, 1949 February-1952 April (Box-folder 30: 24)
    Includes press releases, clippings, and correspondence.
  - John T. Flynn, The Roosevelt Myth, 1949 April-1951 January (Box-folder 29: 12)
    Includes correspondence, newsletters, and newspaper clippings.
  - John T. Flynn, While You Slept, 1952 January-1957 January (Box-folder 31: 11)
  - A. C. Forrest, The Unholy Land, 1973 June-1978 September (Box-folder 39: 15)
  - Aron Gabor, To the East of Man, 1970 April (Box-folder 6: 6)
    Includes manuscript, correspondence, and a Cardinal magazine article.
  - Lyman A. Garber, Of Men and Not of Law, 1965 August-1966 May (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Lyman A. Garber, Of Men and Not of Law, 1965 December-1966 June (Box-folder 30: 29)
    Includes article, reviews, and clippings.
  - Cromwell Gibbons, Republic U.S.A., 1967 January (Box-folder 29: 3)
    Includes summary, reviews, and newspaper clippings.
  - Anatoli M. Granovsky, I Was an NKVD Agent, 1961 October-1962 October (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Anatoli M. Granovsky, I Was an NKVD Agent, 1963 January-August (Box-folder 31: 28)
    Includes reviews, pamphlets, and correspondence.
  - Russell Grenfell, Unconditional Hatred, 1953 October-1961 January (Box-folder 31: 29)
  - Duncan Gleason, The Story of California, undated (Box-folder 48: 8)
  - Albert Gutierrez, The Tragedy of Bolivia, 1958 May-October (Box-folder 31: 6)
    Includes articles and transcripts.
  - Walter Harmer, Mother Magic, 1963 May-1966 October (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Richard Hazelett, The Einstein Myth and The Ives Papers, 1977 November-1981 May (Box-folder 39: 23)